export default [
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 14 / 2 =',
     answer: 7,
    },
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 64 / 4 =',
     answer: 16,
    },
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 15 * 5 =',
     answer: 75,
    },
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 16 * 3 =',
     answer: 48,
    },
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 19 + 57 =',
     answer: 76,
    },
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 28 + 36 =',
     answer: 64,
    },
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 35 - 17 =',
     answer: 18,
    },
    {question: 'вычислите значение: 79 - 23 =',
     answer: 56,
    },
    {question: 'продолжите ряд: 14, 16, 18, ?',
     answer: 20,
    },
    {question: 'продолжите ряд: 34, 31, 28, ?',
     answer: 25,
    },
    {question: 'переведите: apple',
     answer: 'яблоко',
    },
    {question: 'переведите: street',
     answer: 'улица',
    },
    {question: 'переведите: monday',
     answer: 'понедельник',
    },
    {question: 'переведите: brother',
     answer: 'брат',
    },
    {question: 'переведите: window',
     answer: 'окно',
    },
    {question: 'переведите: summer',
     answer: 'лето',
    },
]
